Alright, we're coming out of Executive Session at 09:37.
We have one item to Motion
>> to accept Eric Anderson's
two year contract with the one
change.
Second year salary will be
$92,925.
>> Okay. Do I have a second on that?
I'll second it.
Okay. Scott is saying no further discussion?
All those in favor, aye. Aye.
Scott
and
Paula?
Scott raised his hand. Paula? I can't hear.
Said aye.
Paula? Paula?
Yep.
Aye. Yep.
Is that Paula voted yep. Yep. I said I
>> stopped talking Adrian, because you keep talking over me. I said I three times.
Yep.
Kept missing. It's my fault. It's my fault. I apologize, Paul. All right. Does someone want to make a motion to adjourn?
Oh. So adjourn
>> What? So oh, you know what? Yeah.
Motion to adjourn. No, what would you like?
Adjourn.
Okay.
Motion to adjourn at 09:39.
>> Who's seconding that?
Paula. I'll
second. All right. All those in favor, aye.
All right. Thank you I'm very
sorry I ran a longer meeting.